<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Leah Plofchan</title>
    <link>https://lplofchan.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Leah Plofchan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Leah Plofchan</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lplofchan.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://lplofchan.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lplofchan.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Leah Plofchan and I am pursuing a Bachelor of Science
degree in Computer Science through the College of Engineering at the University
of Notre Dame.  I am interested in software development in cyber security and am
looking for an experience to apply my skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My decision to study Computer Science was not a typical or planned decision.  I
entered Notre Dame in the College of Engineering as an undeclared freshman with
absolutely no interest/background in Computer Science. I really never even
thought about Computer Science until the spring of my Freshman year, when we did
small coding assignments in my Intro to Engineering class.  This small bit of
exposure to Computer Science sparked a serious interest that caused
me to start asking questions and talking to other students/professors. With
barely any experience, I decided to take the risk and change my major to
Computer Science and haven&amp;rsquo;t looked back since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, about a year and a half later, I know that I made the best decision. I am
constantly learning new things and being amazed at all of the cool things that
people are creating in this field.  With this major, I have had the opportunity
to experience awesome programs like the University of Illinois
Urbana-Champagne&amp;rsquo;s HackIllinois hackathon and ThinkChicago, a program aimed at
introducing students to Chicago&amp;rsquo;s growing tech scene.  I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to continue
learning and begin applying my skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am currently studying abroad at University College Dublin in Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>